Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
- Box: 100, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Union Drive for White-Collar Workers, 1963; Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Union Impact on Salaried Personnel, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: White-Collar Unions are Different, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
    Author: George Strauss
  - Item 4: Whitecollar Unions in Australia, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
    Author: R.M. Martin
- Box: 100, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Unions for White-Collar Workers, 1945; Publication (Box 100, Folder 22)
    Notes: May 1945
- Box: 100, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Protest and Irony in Negro Folksong, Publication (Box 100, Folder 23)
- Box: 100, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Wage Policy of White Collar Worker Unions in Sweden, Publication (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Whitecollar Unions in Australia, Publication (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: The TUC and the Non-Manual Worker, Publication (Box 100, Folder 24)
- Box: 101, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Women Returning to the Labour Force A First Report Women's Bureau Careers Centre, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
    Author: Linda Bell
  - Item 2: Facts, Figures Women in the Labour Force, 1969; Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
    Author: Women's Bureau Canada Department of Labour
    Notes: English; French
    Language: English; French.
  - Item 3: Submission By The Canadian Labour Congress To The Royal Commission On The Status of Women, 1968; Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
    Author: Canadian Labour Congres
    Notes: October 1, 1968
  - Item 4: Changing Patterns in Women's Employment, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
    Notes: March 18, 1966
  - Item 5: Job Training for thw mature woman entering or re-entering the labour force, 1964; Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
    Author: Women's Bureau Department of Labour
    Notes: From the Recommendation concerning Vocational Training adopted by the 46th Session of the International Labour Conference in June 1962
  - Item 6: A New Career After 30 The report of an enquiry by the Women's Bureau, 1960; Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Report of a Consultation on the Employment of Women with Family Responsibilities, 1965; Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
    Author: The Women's Burea Department of Labour of Canada
    Notes: February 17, 1965
- Box: 101, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Job Horizons for College Women in the 1960's, 1956-1967 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    Author: W. Willard Wirtz and Mary Dublin Keyerling
    Notes: Dates vary between 1956-1967
- Box: 101, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Married Women Working For Pay In Eight Canadian Cities, 1958; Publication (Box 101, Folder 3)
    Author: Department of Labour Canada
  - Item 2: Occupational Histories of married women working for pay In Eight Canadian Cities, 1959; Publication (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Box: 101, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A Government of Ceylon Legislative Enactments Employment of Females in Mines Ordinance, 1938-1939 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    Author: Government of Ceylon
    Notes: Reprinted from Vol. III of the Revised Edition of the Legislative Enactments of Ceylon (1938(
- Box: 101, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Exploding The Myths A Report of a Conference on Expanding Employment Opportunities for Career Women, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 5)
    Author: Women's Bureau, U.S. Department of Labor and Jeanette Stats
    Notes: December 3, 1966
  - Item 2: Report of the Conference Job Horizons For Women and Girls In The District of Columbia, 1968; Publication (Box 101, Folder 5)
    Author: U.S. Department of Labor George P. Shultz, Wage and Labor Standards Administration, Arthur A. Fletcher, Women's Bureau Elizabeth Duncan Koontz
    Notes: December 6-7, 1968
  - Item 3: Women in the Labor Force, 1962; Publication (Box 101, Folder 5)
    Author: Esther Peterson
    Notes: 1 Nov. 1962
- Box: 101, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Labor Laws Affecting Women A Capsule Summary, 1964; Publication (Box 101, Folder 6)
    Author: U.S. Department of Labor Women's Bureau
    Notes: District of Columbia September 1, 1964
- Box: 101, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Frauenerwerbstatigkeit im internationalen Vergleich, 1970; Publication (Box 101, Folder 7)
    Author: Von Gunter Buttler
- Box: 101, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: L'Emplois Des Femmes Et Ses Problemes Dans Les Etats Membres De La Communaute, Publication (Box 101, Folder 8)
    Author: E. Sullerot
- Box: 101, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Women Workers in Florida, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Women in Florida The Governor's Commission on the Status of Women, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 9)
    Author: The Governor's Commission
- Box: 101, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Some Facts About the Position of Women in the Swedish Labour Market, Publication (Box 101, Folder 10)
    Author: Ingeborg Jonsson
    Notes: Speech at the meeting of the Stockholm Branch of Fredrika Bremer Association, April, 1962
- Box: 101, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Le Travail Des Femmes En France, 1964; Publication (Box 101, Folder 11)
    Author: Francoise Guelaud-Leridon(?) Preface by Jean Fourastie
  - Item 2: Le Travail A Temps Partiel, 1963; Publication (Box 101, Folder 11)
- Box: 101, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Job-Related Expenditures and Management Practices of Gainfully Employed Wives in Four Georgia Cities, 1962; Publication (Box 101, Folder 12)
    Author: Emma G. Holmes
  - Item 2: Women Workers in Georgia, 1960, 1964; Publication (Box 101, Folder 12)
- Box: 101, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Role of Women in Wartime Britain, 1950; Publication (Box 101, Folder 13)
    Author: Margaret M. Fitzpatrick
  - Item 2: Women in Britain, 1964; Publication (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Women and Top Jobs An Interim Report, 1967; Publication (Box 101, Folder 13)
    Author: Michael P. Fogarty, Rhona Rapoport, Robert Rapoport
  - Item 4: Half A Whole Women's Complementary Role in Work and Society, 1969; Publication (Box 101, Folder 13)
    Author: Fawcett Society
  - Item 5: Married Women In Industry, 1954; Publication (Box 101, Folder 13)
    Author: E.M. Harris
  - Item 6: Women Workers in Britain A Handbook, Publication (Box 101, Folder 13)
    Author: Leonora Lloyd
  - Item 7: Women in Britain, 1964; Publication (Box 101, Folder 13)
    Author: Reference Division Central Office of Information
    Notes: This pamphlet is one of a series produced by the Central Office of Information for British Information Services April 1964
  - Item 8: Employing Married Women, 1961; Publication (Box 101, Folder 13)
    Author: Viola Klein
  - Item 9: Working Wives A Survey of Facts and Opinions Concerning the Gainful Employment of Married Women in Britain, 1960; Publication (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Employing women: the employers' view, 1967; Publication (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: a study group young fabian pamphlet 11, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 13)
    Author: Young Fabian Group
- Box: 101, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Mannerarbeit-Frauenarbeit (Die Frau im Handwerk) Drittes Heft der Reihe Betriebe und Beschaftigte des Handwerks in der Bundesrepublik Deutschland, 1956; Publication (Box 101, Folder 14)
- Box: 101, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Mutter-schutz, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 15)
    Author: Erich Bauer and Ursula Luling
  - Item 2: Die Frau im Berufsleben, 1949; Publication (Box 101, Folder 15)
    Author: R. Wagner, O. Korner, H. Neubert
- Box: 101, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Marriage Rate and Women's Employment, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 16)
    Author: Gertrude Williams
    Notes: The Fawcett Lecture 1966-67
  - Item 2: Why is She Away? The Problem of Sickness Among Women in Industry, Publication (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Women in Industry: A Bibliography, 1915; Publication (Box 101, Folder 16)
    Author: Lucy Wyatt Papworth and Dorothy M. Zimmern
- Box: 101, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Women Workers in Illinois, 1960 1/, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Labor Laws Affecting Women A Capsule Summary, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 17)
    Notes: March 1, 1966
  - Item 3: Women Workers in Illinois, 1964; Publication (Box 101, Folder 17)
    Author: John E. Cullerton and Samuel C. Bernstein
    Notes: August, 1964
- Box: 101, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Women in the Working Force in India, 1964; Publication (Box 101, Folder 18)
    Author: D.R. Gadgil
    Notes: Kunda Datar Memorial Lectures 1964
- Box: 101, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Family and Property Law A Capsule Summary Iowa, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Labor Laws Affecting Women A Capsule Summary Iowa, 1965-1966 (Box 101, Folder 19)
    Notes: April 1, 1965-February 1, 1966
- Box: 101, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 101, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Status of Women Workers in Japan, 1959; Publication (Box 101, Folder 20)
    Notes: Possible Japanese characters on the lower right side of the front of the booklet
  - Item 2: Women Workers in Japan, 1964; Publication (Box 101, Folder 20)
    Author: Women's and Minors' Bureau Ministry of Labor Japan
- Box: 101, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 101, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Women Workers in kansas, 1960 (Revised) 1/, Publication (Box 101, Folder 21)
    Notes: Revised July 1966
- Box: 101, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 101, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Labor Laws Affecting Women A Capsule Summary Maine, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 22)
    Notes: February 1, 1966
  - Item 2: Women Workers in Maine, Publication (Box 101, Folder 22)
    Notes: Reissued October 1966
- Box: 101, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 101, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Labor Laws Affecting Women A Capsule Summary Michigan, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Laws and Regulations on Employment of Women in Michigan, Publication (Box 101, Folder 23)
    Author: State of Michigan Department of Labor
  - Item 3: Report of Conference on Women in the Upper Peninsula Economy, 1964; Publication (Box 101, Folder 23)
    Author: W. Willard Wirtz and Mary Dublin Keyserling
    Notes: Held at University Center Northern Michigan University Marquette, Michigan May 16, 1964
- Box: 101, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 101, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Women Workers in Minnesota, 1960 (Revised) 1/, Publication (Box 101, Folder 24)
    Notes: Revised September 1966
  - Item 2: Report of Arrowhead Regional Conference on The Status of Women in Northern Minnesota, 1964; Publication (Box 101, Folder 24)
    Notes: Held at Athletic Club, Duluth, Minn. July 17, 1964
- Box: 101, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 101, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Beyond Our Walls A Plan for Deserving and Getting the Understanding and Support of the Community, 1957; Publication (Box 101, Folder 25)
    Author: Publich and Employee Relations Services Genearl Electric
  - Item 2: Report of the County Executive's Committee on the Education and Employment of Women- Women and Work in Nassau County, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 25)
    Notes: April, 1966
- Box: 101, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 101, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Help Wanted - Female A Study of Demand and Supply in a Local Job Market for Women, Publication (Box 101, Folder 26)
    Author: Georgina M. Smith
- Box: 101, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 101, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Labor Laws Affecting Women A Capsule Summary New Mexico, 1965; Publication (Box 101, Folder 27)
    Notes: March 1, 1965
- Box: 101, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 101, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Women Who Work in Utica, 1947; Publication (Box 101, Folder 28)
    Author: Katherine Alt Smith, Clara A. Hardin, Dorothea Maier and Doris E. Pullman
  - Item 2: An Abstract of Laws Governing the Employment of Women in New York State, 1946; Publication (Box 101, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Long Hours and Night Work Experiences and Views of Women Workers New York State, 1946; Publication (Box 101, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Wartime Changes in the Employment of Women in New York State, 1940-1944, 1945; Publication (Box 101, Folder 28)
    Notes: July 1945
  - Item 5: Employer's Post-War Plans for Women Workers, 1945; Publication (Box 101, Folder 28)
    Author: Division of Women, Child Labor and Minimum Wage
    Notes: January 1945
  - Item 6: Post-War Changes in the Employment of Women in New York State, 1944-1946, Publication (Box 101, Folder 28)
    Author: Division of Industrial Relations, Women in Industry, and Minimum Wage
  - Item 7: Post-War Plans of Women Workers in New York State, 1945; Publication (Box 101, Folder 28)
    Author: Division of Industrial Relations, Women in Industry and Minimum Wage
    Notes: August, 1945
  - Item 8: Why Women Work Financial Responsibilities of Working Women for Self-Support and for Dependents New York State, 1946; Publication (Box 101, Folder 28)
    Notes: March 1946
- Box: 101, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 101, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Employment of Women in The First Post-Reconversion Year in New York State, 1946-1947, Publication (Box 101, Folder 29)
    Author: Division of Industrial Relations Women in Industry and Minimum Wage
    Notes: July 1947
  - Item 2: Women Who Work at Night, 1948; Publication (Box 101, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Employment of Women in New York State - 1940 - 1943, 1944; Publication (Box 101, Folder 29)
    Author: Bureau of Research Division of Women in Industry and Minimum Wage
    Notes: January 1944
  - Item 4: Hours and Night Work of Women in War Plants in New York State, 1945; Publication (Box 101, Folder 29)
    Author: Division of Women ,Child Labor and Minimum Wage
  - Item 5: "What My War Jobs Means", 1944; Publication (Box 101, Folder 29)
    Notes: March 1944
  - Item 6: Home Duties of Working Women in New York State, 1945; Publication (Box 101, Folder 29)
- Box: 101, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 101, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Labor Laws Affecting Women A Capsule Summary North Dakota, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 30)
    Notes: July 1, 1966
- Box: 101, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 101, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Women in the World of Work, 1969; Publication (Box 101, Folder 31)
    Author: Helen Bickel Wolfe
  - Item 2: A Study of Pregnant Women as Unemployment Insurance Claimants in New York State, 1963; Publication (Box 101, Folder 31)
    Author: Ruth Entes
  - Item 3: Women Workers in New York 1/, Publication (Box 101, Folder 31)
    Notes: Revised October 1966
- Box: 101, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 101, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Provisions Regulating Female Labor, 1951; Publication (Box 101, Folder 32)
    Author: Department of Industrial Relations/ Division of Women and Minors
    Notes: Effective - Sept. 17, 1951
  - Item 2: Proceedings Conference on the Chaning Status of Women Focus on Employment, 1963; Publication (Box 101, Folder 32)
    Author: Ohio State Univeristy Columbus
    Notes: Oct. 25 & 26, 1963
  - Item 3: Labor Laws Affecting Women A Capsule Summary Ohio, 1965; Publication (Box 101, Folder 32)
  - Item 4: Women Workers in Ohio, 1960 (Revised) 1/, Publication (Box 101, Folder 32)
  - Item 5: Family and Property Law; A Capsule Summary, Ohio, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 32)
  - Item 6: Labor Laws Affecting Women A Capsule Summary Ohio, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 32)
    Notes: May 1, 1966
  - Item 7: Laws Affecting the Employment of Women, 1967; Publication (Box 101, Folder 32)
    Author: Research Staff of the Legislative Service Commission
    Notes: January, 1967
  - Item 8: Labor Laws Affecting Women A Capsule Summary Ohio, 1967; Publication (Box 101, Folder 32)
    Notes: May 1, 1967
- Box: 101, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 101, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Wages and Hours of Labor of Women and Girls Employed in Mercantile Establishments in Ohio in 1913, 1914; Publication (Box 101, Folder 33)
    Author: M.B. Hammond
- Box: 101, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 101, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Women Workers in Oklahoma, Publication (Box 101, Folder 34)
- Box: 101, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 101, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Women Workers in Oregon 1/, Publication (Box 101, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: Unionism and the General Wage Level, 1950; Publication (Box 101, Folder 35)
    Notes: Reprinted from American Economic Review Volume XL, No. 5, December, 1950
- Box: 101, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 101, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Changing Patterns in Women's Employment, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 36)
    Notes: Report of a Consultation held March 18, 1966
  - Item 2: The Protection of Women Workers & Minors in Poland, 1941; Publication (Box 101, Folder 36)
    Author: The Chief Inspector of Women Labour in Poland (translated by May Bamforth)
- Box: 101, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 101, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Women Workers In Paraguay, 1946; Publication (Box 101, Folder 37)
    Author: U.S. Department of Labor Women's Burea
- Box: 101, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 101, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Labor Laws Affecting Women A Capsule Summary Pennsylvania, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 38)
    Notes: June 1, 1966
  - Item 2: Cost of Living Budget for Employed Women in Pennsylvania, 1960, 1962; Publication (Box 101, Folder 38)
    Author: Bureau of Women Children, Hours and Minimum Wages and Bureau of Research and Statistics, Department of Labor and Industry Commonwealth of Pennsylvania
    Notes: Septemberm, 1962
  - Item 3: Labor Laws Affecting Women A Capsule Summary Pennsylvania, 1965; Publication (Box 101, Folder 38)
    Notes: February 1, 1965
  - Item 4: Regulations Relating to Hours of Work and Conditions of Employment of Women in Pennsylvania, 1965; Publication (Box 101, Folder 38)
    Author: Commonwealth of Pennsylvania Department of Labor and Industry
  - Item 5: Women Workers in Pennsylvania 1/, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 38)
    Author: U.S. Department of Labor U.S. Women's Bureau
    Notes: Revised December 1966
- Box: 101, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 101, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Labor Laws Affecting Women A Capsule Summary Rhode Island, 1965; Publication (Box 101, Folder 39)
- Box: 101, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 101, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Equality of Soviet Women in the Economic Sphere, 1956; Publication (Box 101, Folder 40)
    Author: N. Popova
    Notes: September 1956
  - Item 2: The Working Woman in the Soviet Union, 1932; Publication (Box 101, Folder 40)
    Author: V. Sibiriak
    Notes: Moscow 1932
- Box: 101, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 101, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: The Labor Force Characteristics of Women in Low-Income Rural Areas of the South, 1966; Publication (Box 101, Folder 41)
    Author: Geraldine B. Terry and Alvin L. Bertrand
    Notes: June 1966 Bulletine No. 116
- Box: 101, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 101, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Women Workers in Argentina, Chile, and Uruguay, 1942; Publication (Box 101, Folder 42)
    Author: Frances Perkins and Mary Anderson
- Box: 101, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 101, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Women Workers in Texas 1/, Publication (Box 101, Folder 43)
    Notes: Reissued December 1966
  - Item 2: Labor Laws Affecting Women A Capsule Summary Texas, 1965; Publication (Box 101, Folder 43)
- Box: 101, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Why Women Work, 1946; Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
    Author: United States Department of Labor Women's Bureau
  - Item 2: Women In Factories October 1939 - December 1945 Estimated Number of Women Production Workers Employed in Manufacturing Industries, 1946; Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
    Author: United States Department of Labor Bureau of Labor Statistics Employment Statistics Division
  - Item 3: Employment of Women in the Early Postwar Period With Background of Prewar and War Data, 1946; Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
    Author: Frieda S. Miller and L.B. Schwellenbach
    Notes: Bulletin 211
  - Item 4: Jobs and the Woman, 1945; Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
    Author: Ruth M. Leach
  - Item 5: Women Workers In Ten War Production Areas and Their Postwar Employment Plans, 1946; Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
    Author: L.B. Schwellenbach and Frieda S. Miller
    Notes: Bulletin No. 209
  - Item 6: Women Workers, By Industry, 1944 By Former Activity, Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
  - Item 7: Tables of Working Life for Women, 1950, Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
    Author: James Mitchell and Ewan Clague
    Notes: From the Monthly Labor Review, June August, and October 1956 issues, and additonal material Bulletin No. 1204
  - Item 8: Major Sources of Statistical Data on Employed Woman, 1952; Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
    Author: Women's Bureau U.S. Department of Labor
    Notes: May 21, 1952
  - Item 9: Changes in Women's Employment During the War, 1944; Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
    Author: Mary Elizabeth Pidgeon
    Notes: Special Bulletin No. 20 of the Women's Bureau June 1944
  - Item 10: Standards Governing Employment of Women in Industry, 1918; Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
    Author: The Woman in Industry Service U.S. Department of Labor
    Notes: December 12, 1918
  - Item 11: What Every Working Woman Wants, Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
    Author: Grace Hutchins
  - Item 12: The Workers Bill for Unemployment and Social Insurance, 1935; Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
    Author: Mr. Lundeen
    Notes: January 3, 1935
  - Item 13: Guides for Wartime Use of Women on Fars, 1942; Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
  - Item 14: When You Hire Women, 1944; Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
  - Item 15: Effective Industrial Use of Women in the Defense Program, 1940; Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
    Author: The Women's Bureau U.S. Department of Labor
    Notes: Special Bulletin No. 1
  - Item 16: Lifting and Carrying Weights by Women in Industry, 1941; Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
    Notes: Special Bulletin No. 2 1941 (Revised 1946)
  - Item 17: The Industrial Nurse and The Woman Worker, 1944; Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
    Author: Jennie Mohr
  - Item 18: Child Care Arrangements of Full-Time Working Mothers, 1959; Publication (Box 101, Folder 44)
    Author: Henry C. Lajewski
    Notes: Children's Bureau Publication NO. 378
- Box: 101, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 101, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Training Women Workers A Three-Plant Study, Publication (Box 101, Folder 45)
  - Item 2: Washing and Toilet Facilities For Women In Industry Recommendations for Installation and Maintenance, 1942; Publication (Box 101, Folder 45)
    Notes: Special Bulletin No. 4 of the Women's Bureau
  - Item 3: Women's Jobs Advance and Growth, 1949; Publication (Box 101, Folder 45)
    Author: United States Department of Labor
    Notes: NO. 232
  - Item 4: Careers for Women in the Biological Sciences, 1961; Publication (Box 101, Folder 45)
    Author: Women's Bureau Bulletin
    Notes: Women's Bureau Bulletin 278
  - Item 5: Working Wives and Mothers, 1952; Publication (Box 101, Folder 45)
    Author: Stella B. Applebaum
  - Item 6: Do Good Working Conditions Pay?, 1938; Publication (Box 101, Folder 45)
    Author: Victor G. Heiser
    Notes: New York, December 9, 1938
  - Item 7: The Russell Sage Foundation Library Women In Industry In War-Time, 1917; Publication (Box 101, Folder 45)
    Author: Frederick Warren Jenkins
    Notes: December, 1917